再见
Bye!
-我要搬去亚利桑那州  卖绿松石珠宝  -不要
- I'm gonna move to Arizona and sell turquoise jewelry. - No!
他要打电话给他爸
He's gonna call his dad!
等等  你没告诉他吗
Wait, wait! You didn't tell him?!
完全没说
Not at all.
完蛋了
Holy crap!
我们必须阻止他
We have to stop him.
或许不用
Or maybe we don't.
仔细想想
Think it through.
他的某个垃圾姐妹接了电话
One of the trash-bag sisters picks up.
一阵困惑之后
Confusion, confusion.
你个死混球
Oy, ya daft fart.
我们给你寄了讣告  爸爸死了
We sent the obit. Da's dead.
然后  突然跳到几周之后
And boom! A couple of weeks from now,
我身上会形成一道不爽猫形状的美黑线
I have a tan line shaped like Grumpy Cat,
因为在巡游船的甲板上  它一直坐在我的大腿上
because she's been sitting on my lap on the cruise deck...
格雷琴  现在轮不到你来发号施令了
Gretchen, you don't get to be in charge anymore!
什么  你不能这么做
What? You can't do that.
一切都听我家男人指挥
My man takes charge.